A Guide to the Cora C. Curry Papers, 1804-1966
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Cora C. Curry Papers, 1804-1966
The Library of Virginia
27622
9.9 cubic feet
Curry, Cora C.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Papers presented to the Archives by the Reverend Anthony Jacob Henckel Family National Association, per Mr. R. C. Hinkle, Jr., Badin, North Carolina, 29 September 1971.
Biographical Information
Cora C. Curry was historian of the Henckel Family Association.
Scope and Content
Papers contain the correspondence of Cora C. Curry and her research notes concerning Henckel family genealogy, as well as copies of some letters and early documents used in her research. Also included are some letters and notes of those who worked on the publication of the Henckel family genealogy after Curry's death in 1944, primarily Minnie W. Junkin and Burt B. Barker.
See also Burt B. Barker Papers (Acc. 27623) and Harrison M. Calhoun Papers (Acc. 35990).
Contents List
- Cora C. Curry Papers, 1804-1966., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 1-22)
  - Correspondence of Henckel family and re: Henckel family, 1804-1911. (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1912-1920. (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1921-1925. (Box 3)
  - Correspondence, 1926-1927. (Box 4)
  - Correspondence, 1927-1930. (Box 5)
  - Correspondence, 1930-1931. (Box 6)
  - Correspondence, 1932-1934. (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, 1934-1936. (Box 8)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1938. (Box 9)
  - Correspondence, 1939-1949. (Box 10)
  - Correspondence, 1950 - undated. (Box 11)
  - Correspondence, postcards - Genealogical research notes, Henckel family, A-N (Box 12)
  - Genealogical research notes, Henckel family, P-S - Compiled notes. (Box 13)
  - Genealogical research notes, Henckel family, Compiled notes, volumes. (Box 14)
  - Genealogical research notes, Henckel family, Rough notes - Rough notes, volumes. (Box 15)
  - Genealogical research notes, Henckel family, Rough notes, volumes. (Box 16)
  - Genealogical research notes, related families, A-R. (Box 17)
  - Genealogical research notes, related families, S-Y - Miscellaneous related families, A-Y. (Box 18)
  - Miscellaneous related families - Genealogical research notes, Charts. (Box 19)
  - Genealogical research notes, Documents - Henckel Family Association and Reunion, Clippings, printed material and notes. (Box 20)
  - Henckel buildings, coats of arms, photographs, relics, and tombstones - Printed material, German. (Box 21)
  - Stamps - Curry Personal Papers, Gleason genealogy. (Box 22)